http://www.mazaklaser.com/privacy-policy/

Technology
AutomationSoftwareHigh Performance AirMazak iSMART Factory™Mazak SmartBox
Back
News & Events
Company NewsPress ReleasesCustomer SuccessesUpcoming EventsBlog
Customer Support
Applications SupportService SupportParts SupportTrainingService PromotionsMeet the TeamTech Tips
solutions including CNC controls and automation systems.
Technology
AutomationSoftwareHigh Performance AirMazak iSMART Factory™Mazak SmartBox
News & Events
Company NewsPress ReleasesCustomer SuccessesUpcoming EventsBlog
Technology Center
Technology Center
Elgin
Customer Support
Applications SupportService SupportParts SupportTrainingService PromotionsMeet the TeamTech Tips
Mazak Optonics Corporation Digital Privacy Policy
Mazak Optonics Corporation Digital Privacy Practices - Your Privacy is a Priority to Us.
Personal Information
In general, you can visit Mazak Optonics Corporation on the Web without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you. You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to process an order or to provide you with a service. It is our intent to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you on the Internet. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.
Information security and quality
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested. Cookies, web beacons and other technologies we sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our site to help us provide better customer service. This anonymous information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." Mazak Optonics Corporation may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. Also, when we collect personal data from you in connection with a transaction we may extract some information about that transaction in an anonymous format and combine it with other anonymous information such as clickstream data. This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can disable your cookies. We collect the anonymous information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Some Mazak Optonics Corporation pages use cookies or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not function properly. We may also use Web beacon technologies to better tailor those sites to provide better customer service. These "Web beacons" are placed on a number of pages across the Mazak Optonics Corporation Web sites. When a visitor accesses these pages, an anonymous notice of that visit is generated which may be processed by us or by our vendors. These Web beacons work in conjunction with cookies. If you don't want to associate your anonymous cookie information with your visits to these pages, you can set your browser to turn off cookies. If you turn off cookies, web beacon technologies will still detect anonymous visits to these pages, but the notices they generate cannot be associated with other anonymous cookie information and are disregarded.
Personalized URL link
On occasion, Mazak Optonics Corporation presents a personalized URL (link) that brings the visitor to a personalized Web page. Such a personal URL is readily identifiable and by clicking on that link and going to a personal Web page you are agreeing to let Mazak Optonics Corporation collect information about your session visits. We use this information to help us provide you with information that matches your interests. If you do not wish information to be used in this way, simply do not click on such personalized URLs.
Children's data
While neither Corporation are directed towards children, we are committed to comply with applicable laws and requirements, such as the United States' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
Privacy technology
Technology will increasingly help you to have more control over your personal information. It will also help organizations to manage their privacy practices and policies. As an information technology provider, Mazak Optonics Corporation actively supports the development of privacy technologies to help achieve these goals, and to help create greater trust and confidence in the way personal information is handled. Products and services are available which can help give you privacy protection while navigating the Web. See http://www.privacyalliance.org/resources/rulesntools.shtml for an overview of many privacy-related tools. Please note that Mazak Optonics Corporation has not formally evaluated all of these tools.
Business relationships
Mazak Optonics Corporation sites may contain links to other Web sites. Mazak Optonics Corporation is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
This privacy statement was last updated on December 27, 2013. Mazak Optonics Corporation reserves the right to modify this document at any time.
Copyright © 2016 Mazak Optonics Corporation. All rights reserved.
Products and specifications subject to change without notice.
Facebook:
facebook.com/MazakOptonics
LinkedIn:
linkedin.com/company/mazak-optonics-corporation
YouTube:
youtube.com/MazakOptonics
